I'm hungry! Yoshino!
Yoshino?
Yoshino? Are you not here?
That's strange.
Hey, Narino. Do you know where Yoshino is?
What's wrong?
I got hungry right before
I was supposed to leave,
so I thought I'd have her make me something.
My sister went out shopping.
Shopping? That's strange.
Did I ask her to get me something?
No, I asked her to get something.
And I told her to buy something
for herself, too.
I see.
Otherwise, she'd never do
anything for herself,
considering she's stuck in errand girl mode.
#8 "There Are Things You Shouldn't Realize"
Pig's Foot...
Master...
Grapel
Well...
Bye.
Ow!
Are you hurt?
The biggest blunder of my life...
What nonsense are you going on about?
You sprained your ankle, didn't you?
I'm fine.
Anyway, this isn't the best place.
Let's go somewhere else.
Why do you have brass knuckles?!
I can't hold back when my life is in danger.
Why are you saying that
with such a serious face?!
Well, can you move, then?!
She moves like she's ancient.
See? You can't walk, right?
At least make it a piggyback ride...
That's what this was about?
Aki-sama's late...
Last time, Aki-sama canceled
because she said something came up.
Yes. This social gathering between
Aki-sama and us, her bodyguards...
has been either canceled or
delayed three times out of five.
And they're all due to that incident!
Ever since rumors started going around about
Aki-sama going out with Makabe Masamune!
Rumors... about them going out?
A-A moment, please. I'm not sure
if "rumor" is quite the right word...
I called it a rumor because it is a rumor!
It's basically an urban legend!
I'd rather not admit it myself...
But it is a known fact that Aki-sama
and Makabe Masamune are dating.
I won't accept it!
You need to face reality!
But I don't wanna!
It's a rumor! It's just a rumor,
dang it! Aki-sama!
Hang on a sec! No good is going
to come of us fighting over this!
Today's just gonna have to
be the day we ask Aki-sama
how the hell she ended up going out
with that Makabe Masamune!
I still believe in the theory
that Makabe's tricking her!
Well, of course he is!
B-But...
If there's just a slight chance...
no, even a sliver of a chance
that Aki-sama really has feelings
for Makabe Masamune...
If she does?
Perhaps she may think us worrying about her
is nothing more than a nuisance, and...
Then... Then what are we supposed to do?!
Oh, yeah! Ever since it was reported
at the end of last year that
Aki-sama was going out with Makabe,
she's never given us a proper explanation!
To be honest, I have no idea
how we should even approach this.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
A-Aki-sama...
Um, er...
Y-You look... radiant... today...
People keep staring at us.
But more importantly...
Am I heavy?
No, not really!
She'd kill me for saying this, but...
Her boobs are squished
so tight against my back...
She'd just snap my neck like... "crack."
Master can get pretty violent at times...
But this weight and sensation...
No, no, no! If she ever found out
I was worried about that...
Pig's Foot.
Did she figure me out?! I'm gonna die!
You can put me down.
There's a park over there.
I'll be fine if I rest there.
Oh...
What are you talking about?
You don't need to be—
I'm wearing a skirt, and
people might see my panties!
Okay, we can go over there.
Make it extra quick.
This whole time, I was
worried about her boobs,
and she was worried about
something completely different...
I'm sorry, everyone.
I haven't been able to match my
schedule with all of yours lately.
I-It's okay...
W-We're not worried about that.
Y-You needn't worry about us.
Hey, ask her the question already.
Me?! But I can't!
Oh, fine.
Um, so... Aki-sama...
Yes?
How are things going for you lately?
What things?
You know... Are you...
enjoying the sweet life?
Sweet?
Oh, you mean sweets?
Yeah, I've been eating them quite often.
You didn't get through to her at all!
This is the best I can do.
Very well...
A-Aki-sama...
Yes?
Is... Is... your...
Isn't the moon lovely?!
It's the middle of the day.
I-I'm sunk...
Private Mizuno!
Hey, what's going on?
You're all acting strange today.
Did something happen?
Wh-What the...
We want to know how you really feel!
How I... really feel?
Are you really going out
with Makabe Masamune?!
She said it!
Even through her panic, she managed
an attack right to the core!
Well... yes...
That's...
The embarrassed face a girl
makes when she's in love.
I never thought I'd see
Aki-sama make this face.
I hate to admit it, but...
I love this side of her, too!
There we go.
Are you okay?
You don't need to touch me!
Okay, okay.
I haven't seen her in so long,
and she treats me like this...
She really doesn't back off.
The birthday date...
You chased Aki-sama away?
The one thing I really didn't want
her to ask me about right now!
Play it off!
D-Don't make it sound so bad!
We just wrapped things up
a bit earlier than planned!
You know, the fact that I wasn't
so pushy makes me a gentleman,
and most girls would think, "Wow, how
lovely!" and my likability would go up.
Don't give me that.
Aki-sama's super depressed right now.
Well, I think it's weird, too.
But... my body's not cooperating.
Ow!
Can you promise me you'll throw her
onto the bed the next time you see her?
I absolutely cannot!
How are you so pathetic?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Pig's Foot?
Could it be...
Pardon me a sec.
Pig's Foo—
I was right. With you, it's okay.
I never should've gone out with her.
I think I had the most fun when
I was devising my plan with you.
Master?
We want to know how you really feel!
Well, so do I...
Aki-chan?
Kanetsugu?
It's... been a while.
Yeah...
Do you... have a second?
Sure...
Ow!
Why'd she headbutt me all of a sudden?
Huh?
Where'd she go?
She can't walk on that leg.
I'll pretend you
never said that
She's right. I shouldn't have said that.
For Adagaki-san's sake...
And for Master's sake.
How stupid am I?
No matter how much I regret it,
I can't take it back now.
I was pretty surprised.
I never would've thought
I'd run into you out there.
Yeah.
I think this is the first time
we've talked since that incident.
Yeah.
Kanetsugu?!
Aki-chan, I'm so sorry!
I'm not expecting you to completely forgive me.
But I...
Lift your head, please.
I heard the details.
You've basically worked things
out with my father, right?
Yeah...
So your sister's in the hospital?
And you needed money for that.
Don't get the wrong idea.
There's nothing to forgive. I'm not even mad.
But it's still true that I was
lying to you that whole time.
It's also true that it's been weighing
on your mind and you regret it, right?
I know that because that's
the kind of person you are.
Besides, it's all in the past now.
You're so strong, Aki-chan.
No, I'm not.
You had something you wanted
to protect, even if it meant
making some sacrifices
with those around you.
You did all that because
you had the resolve, right?
But I'm different.
I had no idea I'd been hurting
a certain someone...
apparently.
I'm going to get revenge
on that woman!!
Even though I know that now,
I can't do anything.
I can't even be brave enough
to accept that fact.
I'm not strong at all.
This certain someone...
Are you talking about...
Makabe-kun?
Aki-chan, you're dating Makabe-kun, right?
I didn't think you two would actually
start dating after that confession.
I know it's going to be hard to
convince you, considering
I'd been lying to you that whole time...
But because I'd been lying
that whole time, I can say this.
The one thing you can't do
is lie to your own heart.
Lie to my own heart?
All this time...
I thought that maintaining the Gasou
family's financial power and status
was the way to protect my family.
gaki Group
Secretary
I'd convinced myself that I had to
do whatever it took to do that.
But all I was doing was lying
to myself that whole time.
When you all found out everything,
it became clear to me that my family's
financial power and status meant nothing.
The one thing that mattered to
me was my little sister's smile.
Everything I did was for my sister.
When I realized that, I figured out
what I really wanted to do.
So, right now...
I feel really refreshed.
I see...
Are you able to accept
your feelings right now?
My... feelings?
You can't end up like me.
Accept... my feelings...
I get it. I...
Welcome home, Yoshino.
I heard you went shopping.
Well? Did you find anything nice?
No, I...
Yoronpas
Tape
Includes 6
Ointment
Nikixin
Keshiro
Patappu – Pills
What? The first-aid kit?
I twisted my ankle.
Wait, you sprained it?! That's no good!
Honestly, you're such a klutz.
Here, have a seat. I'll treat you.
I'm fine...
Just sit already.
Ow!
This is really bad...
I'm honestly pretty surprised myself.
How did you even walk home like this?
Perseverance!
What?!
Anyway, all we can do now is ice it.
Make sure you go to the hospital tomorrow.
Okay.
Aki-sama, thank you very much.
What are you talking about?
Anyone would do this much.
Would they, though?
I'm a traitorous witch.
Even what happened today...
Yoshino?
No...
No, no, no...
I think I had the most fun when
I was devising my plan with you.
This absolutely cannot happen...
Why would you say
something like that, you idiot?
Morning!
Morning, Makabe-kun.
H-Hey... Morning.
Huh?
What?
Oh, I just realized you're by yourself today.
By myself? What are you—
Oh, no!
I'm on duty in class today,
so I have to get there early!
I'll see you later!
You sure are busy bright and early.
That's a big yawn.
Koiwai-san.
Don't call me that.
You're supposed to call me Yoshino, remember?
Th-This is...
This isn't right!
A dream?
I think there are some feelings
that you should really never accept.